Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences Records UA195
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences Records
1988 -- 2011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
Dean of the School of Arts and Sciences
UA195
21.2 Linear Feet 17 boxes
3 Digital Object(s)
1.2 Gigabytes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into ten series: Correspondence; Appointment books; Building and construction plans and projects; Reports; Faculty information sheets; Subject files; Meeting minutes; Orientation; Faculty forum and events; and Unprocessed accessions.
Related Materials
UA045, Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences, and Engineering, DCA.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences was created in 2001 from a division of the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences and Engineering. The Dean of Arts and Sciences is responsible for all undergraduate and graduate departments and programs, as well as research centers and institutes under the scope of Arts and Sciences. The School of Arts and Sciences comprises the College of Liberal Arts, the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, as well as the College of Special Studies.
The Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences reports to the Office of the University Provost/Senior Vice President. The Dean of Arts and Sciences works closely with a Leadership Team comprised of Deans of Academic Affairs and Education at both the undergraduate and the graduate level.
Susan Ernst served as Dean of Liberal Arts and Jackson College for Natural and Social Sciences from 1997 to the split of the Office in 2001. In 2001 she was named the Dean of Arts and Sciences, a position she held until 2005. Kevin Dunn served as Assistant Dean of Academic Affairs within the Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences from 2002-2005.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Scope and Contents
The collection documents the activities of the Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences. This collection contains correspondence, appointment books, reports submitted to the Office, faculty information sheets, building and construction plans, and meeting minutes from 2001 to the 2010s. Significant topics include matriculation; donor relations; Task Forces; Faculty Forum and other events; New Faculty and New Chair Orientation sessions; and Special projects.
Administration and Governance -- Planning, evaluation, policies & procedures; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty; Facilities
- Correspondence, 2001 -- 2010; UA195.001; 5.05 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of correspondence generated from the Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences. The bulk of the correspondence is thank you letters to donors.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Susan Ernst correspondence, thank you letters, and chronological files, 2001 -- 2005; UA195.001.001
    Open for research.
    - Ernst-Chronological, 2001; UA195.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
      20 years from date of creation.
    - Ernst-Chronological, 2001 -- 2002; UA195.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Ernst-Chronological, 2002; UA195.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Ernst-Chonological, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Thank You: Letters to major Donors [1 of 3], 2003; UA195.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - Thank You: Letters to major Donors [2 of 3], 2003; UA195.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Thank You: Letters to major Donors [3 of 3], 2003; UA195.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Thank you letters [1 of 4], 2004; UA195.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - Thank you letters [2 of 4], 2004; UA195.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - Thank you letters [3 of 4], 2004; UA195.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - Thank you letters [4 of 4], 2004; UA195.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Thank You Letters [1 of 3], 2004; UA195.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - Thank You Letters [2 of 3], 2004; UA195.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - Thank You Letters [3 of 3], 2004; UA195.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    - Development Letters [1 of 3], 2004; UA195.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - Development Letters [2 of 3], 2004; UA195.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    - Development Letters [3 of 3], 2004; UA195.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    - Thank You Letters [1 of 3], 2005; UA195.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    - Thank You Letters [2 of 3], 2005; UA195.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    - Thank You Letters [3 of 3], 2005; UA195.001.002.00001 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
    - Thank You Letters [1 of 3], 2005; UA195.001.002.00002 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
    - Thank You Letters [2 of 3], 2005; UA195.001.002.00003 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
    - Thank You Letters [3 of 3], 2005; UA195.001.002.00004 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
    - Ernst-Chronological [Folder 1 of 2], 2003 -- 2004; UA195.001.004.00001 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Ernst-Chronological [Folder 2 of 2], 2003 -- 2004; UA195.001.004.00002 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Matriculation 03 to (Dean's File), 2003 -- 2004; UA195.001.004.00003 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Ernst- Chronological [Folder 1 of 2], 2004 -- 2005; UA195.001.004.00004 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Ernst- Chronological [Folder 2 of 2], 2004 -- 2005; UA195.001.004.00005 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Dunn correspondence, 2002 -- 2006; UA195.001.002
    - Dean Dunn's Class, 2003; UA195.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - TAS Class, 2003; UA195.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Task Force on Leadership, 2005; UA195.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - Value Added Task Force, 2005; UA195.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - Mentoring Program, 2005; UA195.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - Task Force on Instruction, 2005; UA195.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - Chronological File, 2002; UA195.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
    - Chron File for, 2003; UA195.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
    - Chronological File, 2004; UA195.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
    - Chronological File, 2005; UA195.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
    - [Correspondence], 2006; UA195.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Sullivan correspondence, 2006 -- 2010; UA195.001.003
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2006; UA195.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00032 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00033 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00034 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2007; UA195.001.008.00035 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2008; UA195.001.008.00036 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2008; UA195.001.008.00037 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2008; UA195.001.008.00038 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2008; UA195.001.008.00039 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2008; UA195.001.008.00040 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron., 2008; UA195.001.008.00041 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan chron file, 2008; UA195.001.008.00042 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan chron file, 2009; UA195.001.008.00043 (Box 8)
    - Leave Approval/Denial Letter, 2009; UA195.001.008.00044 (Box 8)
    - 2nd - and 4th - year reviews, 2009; UA195.001.008.00045 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan Chron File, 2010; UA195.001.008.00046 (Box 8)
  - Sternberg correspondence, 2005 -- 2010; UA195.001.004
    - Sternberg Chron., 2005; UA195.001.009.00001 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2005; UA195.001.009.00002 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2005; UA195.001.009.00003 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2005; UA195.001.009.00004 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00005 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00006 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00007 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00008 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00009 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00010 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00011 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00012 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00013 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00014 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00015 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2006; UA195.001.009.00016 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00017 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00018 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00019 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00020 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00021 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00022 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00023 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00024 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00025 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00026 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00027 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2007; UA195.001.009.00028 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00029 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00030 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00031 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00032 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00033 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00034 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00035 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00036 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00037 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00038 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00039 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2008; UA195.001.009.00040 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00041 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00042 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00043 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00044 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00045 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00046 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00047 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00048 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00049 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00050 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00051 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2009; UA195.001.009.00052 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2010; UA195.001.009.00053 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron.0, 2010; UA195.001.009.00054 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2010; UA195.001.009.00055 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2010; UA195.001.009.00056 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2010; UA195.001.009.00057 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
    - Sternberg Chron., 2010; UA195.001.009.00058 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
      Folder empty.
- Appointment Books, 1997 -- 2008; UA195.002; 1.45 Linear Feet
  This series contains appointment books from the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences. Multiple Deans within the Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences are represented in this series. The appointment books of Susan Ernst, whose term within the Office covers both before and after the split of the Office, are housed in this collection.
  This series is arranged chronologically by Dean.
  - [Ernst Appointment Book], 1997 -- 1998; UA195.002.002.00005 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Ernst Appointment Book], 1998; UA195.002.002.00006 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Ernst Appointment Book], 1999; UA195.002.002.00007 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Ernst Appointment Book], 2000; UA195.002.002.00008 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Ernst Appointment Book], 2001; UA195.002.002.00009 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Ernst Appointment Book], 2002; UA195.002.002.00010 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Ernst Appointment Book], 2003; UA195.002.002.00011 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Ernst Appointment Book], 2004; UA195.002.002.00012 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Dunn Appointment Book], 2001 -- 2002; UA195.002.002.00013 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Dunn Appointment Book], 2002 -- 2003; UA195.002.002.00014 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Dunn Appointment Book], 2003 -- 2004; UA195.002.002.00015 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Dunn Appointment Book], 2004 -- 2005; UA195.002.002.00016 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - [Dunn Appointment Book], 2005 -- 2006; UA195.002.009.00059 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
  - [Dunn Appointment Book], 2006 -- 2007; UA195.002.009.00060 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
  - [Dunn Appointment Book], 2007 -- 2008; UA195.002.009.00061 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
  - Dept. Correspondence [Sullivan Appointment Book], 2006; UA195.002.009.00062 (Box UA195 Shared 3)
- Building and Construction Plans and Projects, 2002 -- 2007; UA195.003; 3.6 Linear Feet
  This series consists of construction plans and reports for building and construction projects related to Arts and Sciences Departments.
  This series is not arranged.
  - Tufts Music Building Design Development Report, 2004; UA195.003.002.00017 (Box UA195 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Music Building Architectural Plans, 2004; UA195.003.003.00001 (Box Shared 128)
  - Space Planning Materials from Chairs, 2004; UA195.003.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Space Planning Meetings, 2004; UA195.003.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Campus Master Plan, 2002 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Space Planning, 2004; UA195.003.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Summer Renovation Project, 2004; UA195.003.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Expansion/Renovation Project Spring, 2007; UA195.003.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Meetings with William Rawn Associates, 2004; UA195.003.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Integrated Lab Facility, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Arts, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Natural Sciences, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Social Sciences, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Humanities, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Departmental Space Information, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Space Inventory, 2004; UA195.003.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - 200 Boston Ave., 2005; UA195.003.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Building Projects, Biology, Integrated Labratory Complex (ILC), 2005; UA195.003.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Dance Studio, 2005; UA195.003.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Building Projects, Music Building, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Department Plans Space Planning Integrated Lab, 2004 -- 2005; UA195.003.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - [Tufts University Master Plan: Interim Report], 2004; UA195.003.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - [Tufts University Master Plan: Final Draft: Square Footage Capacity], 2005; UA195.003.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - [Tufts University Master Plan: Final Draft: Executive Summary], 2005; UA195.003.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - [Tufts University Master Plan: Draft Final Report], 2005; UA195.003.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - [Building, department, room type, area distribution report], 2005; UA195.003.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - [Building, department, room type, area distribution report], 2005; UA195.003.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - William Rawls Master Planning Services RFP [binder, folder 1 of 3], 2003; UA195.003.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - William Rawls Master Planning Services RFP [binder, folder 2 of 3], 2003; UA195.003.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - William Rawls Master Planning Services RFP [binder, folder 3 of 3], 2003; UA195.003.010.00028 (Box 10)
- Reports, 1995 -- 2007; UA195.004; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series consists of department reports submitted to the Dean of Arts and Sciences.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Annual Reports, 1998 -- 2003; UA195.004.001
    - Africa and the New World, 2001; UA195.004.004.00006 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - American Studies Program, 2000 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00007 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Biology, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00008 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Chemistry, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00009 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Child Development, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00010 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Classics, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00011 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Community Health, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00012 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Comparative Religion, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00013 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Day Care Center, 2001 -- 2002; UA195.004.004.00014 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Drama and Dance, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00015 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Drama and Dance, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00016 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Education, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00017 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Education, 1999 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00018 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Environmental Studies, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00019 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Experimental College, 1998 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00020 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Geology, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00021 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - GRALL, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00022 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Global Leadership Program, 2001 -- 2002; UA195.004.004.00023 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Health Ed., 2000 -- 2002; UA195.004.004.00024 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - History, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00025 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - International Relations, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00026 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Mathematics, 2002; UA195.004.004.00027 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Museum School, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00028 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Music, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00029 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Occupational Therapy, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00030 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Peace & Justice Studies, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00031 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Philosophy, 1999 -- 2001; UA195.004.004.00032 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Physics & Astronomy, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00033 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Political Science, 1999 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00034 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Psychology, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00035 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Sociology & Anthropolgy, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00036 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Romance Languages, 1998 -- 2002; UA195.004.004.00037 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - UEP (Urban & Environ. Policy & Planning), 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00038 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Visual & Critical Studies, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00039 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - Wright Center, 2001; UA195.004.004.00040 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
    - [Untitled], 2000 -- 2003; UA195.004.004.00041 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
      The folder contains annual reports from the Dean of Academic Affairs, Administration and Finance, Dean of the Graduate School, Dean of the Undergraduate School, the Diversity Office, and the Provost
  - Student Surveys, 1995 -- 2007; UA195.004.002
    - Surveys, 1995 -- 1997; UA195.004.011.00001 (Box 11)
    - Surveys, 1998 -- 2000; UA195.004.011.00002 (Box 11)
    - Surveys Historical Trends, 1998 -- 2003; UA195.004.011.00003 (Box 11)
      1998-99; 2001-03
    - Senior Surveys, 2001; UA195.004.011.00004 (Box 11)
    - Senior Surveys Reports, 2001; UA195.004.011.00005 (Box 11)
    - Sophomore Survey, 2002; UA195.004.011.00006 (Box 11)
    - BOST Marketing Survey, 2002; UA195.004.011.00007 (Box 11)
    - Surveys[1 of 2], 2002; UA195.004.011.00008 (Box 11)
    - Surveys [2 of 2], 2002; UA195.004.011.00009 (Box 11)
    - Surveys, 2003; UA195.004.011.00010 (Box 11)
    - Surveys [1 of 2], 2004; UA195.004.011.00011 (Box 11)
    - Surveys [2 of 2], 2004; UA195.004.011.00012 (Box 11)
    - Senior Surveys [1 of 3], 2005; UA195.004.011.00013 (Box 11)
    - Senior Surveys [2 of 3], 2005; UA195.004.011.00014 (Box 11)
    - Senior Surveys [3 of 3], 2005; UA195.004.011.00015 (Box 11)
    - Surveys [1 of 2], 2006; UA195.004.011.00016 (Box 11)
    - Surveys [2 of 2], 2006; UA195.004.011.00017 (Box 11)
    - Senior Surveys, 2007; UA195.004.011.00018 (Box 11)
- Faculty Information Sheets, 1990 -- 2008; UA195.005; 5.35 Linear Feet
  This series is composed of Faculty Information Sheets. The Faculty Information Sheets are records completed by faculty members to report their class loads, research goals and progress, and current publications to the Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences for each academic year. These records primarily start in 2001, the year the Office of the Dean of Arts, Sciences and Engineering split into two separate offices, but some records predate the split. Due to the close relationship of the records to each other and arrangement at the time they were received, DCA decided not to separate the records.
  - Art & Art History, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00042 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Biology, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00043 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - BSOT, 1999 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00044 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Chemistry, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00045 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Child Development, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00046 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Classics, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00047 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Community Health, 1994 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00048 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Community Health Program, 1994 -- 1995; UA195.005.004.00049 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Drama & Dance, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00050 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Economics, 2001 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00051 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - Education, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00052 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - English, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.004.00053 (Box UA195 Shared 2)
  - German, Russian, &Asian Languages & Literatures, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Geology, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - History, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Mathematics, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Music, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Philosophy, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Physics, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Political Science, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Psychology, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Comparative Religion, Asian Studies, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Romance Languages, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Sociology & Anthropology, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Urban and Environmental Policy & Planning, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Visual and Critical Studies, 2002 -- 2003; UA195.005.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Art & Art History, 2000 -- 2005; UA195.005.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Biology, 1998 -- 2005; UA195.005.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Chemistry, 1996 -- 2006; UA195.005.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Child Development [Folder 1 of 2], 1996 -- 2006; UA195.005.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Child Development [Folder 2 of 2], 1994 -- 2006; UA195.005.005.00019 (Box 5)